(Penny:)You're a pig, Howard.
(Howard:)How is doable
anything but a compliment?
- Why don't we work on the robot?
- Please, Leonard, not now.
(Howard:)Once again, Penny and I
have begun our little tango.
Our... Our tango?
(Howard:)The carnal repartee, the erotic to and fro.
(Howard:)But as delicious
as the appetizer might be...
(Howard:)...at some point we will have to succumb
and eat the entrée while it's still...
[MIMICS SIZZLING]
(Howard:)...hot.
(Leonard:)I'm begging you, stop talking.
(Penny:)Look, normally, I can just ignore you.
(Penny:)I mean, I get it. You're a little peculiar.
Like Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, excuse me, Penny, but in this room,
you're the one who's peculiar.
(Penny:)Yeah, you might be right.
But back to you. You think you're some
sort of smooth-talking ladies' man...